http://www.jeffhayes.com/privacy-policy/

Jeff Hayes Fine Arts Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy will explain how Jeff Hayes Fine Arts uses the personal data we collect from you when you use our website.Topics:What data do we collect?How do we collect your data?How will we use your data?How do we store your data?MarketingWhat are your data protection rights?What are cookies?How do we use cookies?What types of cookies do we use?How to manage your cookiesPrivacy policies of other websitesChanges to our privacy policyHow to contact usHow to contact the appropriate authoritiesWhat data do we collect?Jeff Hayes Fine Arts collects the following data:Personal identification information (Name, email address, phone number, mailing address, IP address)Financial information needed to process purchases. This information is not stored, but passed directly to Stripe, an industry-standard credit card processor.How do we collect your data?You directly provide Jeff Hayes Fine Arts with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:Register online or place an order for any of our products or services.Voluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback on any of our message boards or via email.Use or view our website via your browser’s cookies.How will we use your data?Jeff Hayes Fine Arts collects your data so that we can:Process your order and manage your account.Email you with special offers on other products and services we think you might like.Create “Lookalike” data sets – groups of people with similar characteristics to you.If you agree, Jeff Hayes Fine Arts will share your data with our partner companies so that they may offer you their products and services.(We currently do not share your data with any partner companies.)When Jeff Hayes Fine Arts processes your order, it may send your data to, and also use the resulting information from, credit reference agencies to prevent fraudulent purchases.How do we store your data?Jeff Hayes Fine Arts securely stores your data at ActiveCampaign, an industry-standard email service provider. Some data is stored within the website directly, using 2-factor authentication and industry-standard security measures. Backups are stored in industry-standard cloud storage with 2-factor authentication and encryption. Data required to process credit card transactions is not stored, but passed directly to Stripe, a credit card processor.Jeff Hayes Fine Arts will keep your data until you request its deletion.MarketingJeff Hayes Fine Arts would like to send you information about products and services of ours that we think you might like, as well as those of our partner companies.(We currently do not share your data with any partner companies.)If you have agreed to receive marketing, you may always opt out at a later date.You have the right at any time to stop Jeff Hayes Fine Arts from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your data to other members of the Jeff Hayes Fine Arts Group.If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please click here.What are your data protection rights?Jeff Hayes Fine Arts would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:The right to access – You have the right to request Jeff Hayes Fine Arts for copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.The right to rectification – You have the right to request that Jeff Hayes Fine Arts correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request Jeff Hayes Fine Arts to complete the information you believe is incomplete.The right to erasure – You have the right to request that Jeff Hayes Fine Arts erase your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that Jeff Hayes Fine Arts restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to Jeff Hayes Fine Arts’s processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to data portability – You have the right to request that Jeff Hayes Fine Arts transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us by using this contact form.CookiesCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technologyFor further information, visit allaboutcookies.org.How do we use cookies?Jeff Hayes Fine Arts uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:Providing a seamless experience with other websites you may visit, and presenting products you may be interested in on Facebook and Instagram.What types of cookies do we use?There are a number of different types of cookies, however, our website uses:Advertising – Jeff Hayes Fine Arts uses these cookies to collect information about your visit to our website, the content you viewed, the links you followed and information about your browser, device, and your IP address. Jeff Hayes Fine Arts sometimes shares some limited aspects of this data with third parties for advertising purposes. We may also share online data collected through cookies with our advertising partners. This means that when you visit another website, you may be shown advertising based on your browsing patterns on our website.How to manage cookiesYou can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.Privacy policies of other websitesThe Jeff Hayes Fine Arts website contains links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.Changes to our privacy policyJeff Hayes Fine Arts keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on November 1, 2019.How to contact usIf you have any questions about Jeff Hayes Fine Arts’s privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.Use this contact form.How to contact the appropriate authorityShould you wish to report a complaint or if you feel that Jeff Hayes Fine Arts has not addressed your concern in a satisfactory manner, you may contact the Information Commissioner’s Office.
